<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aenism</title>
    <link>https://aenism.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Aenism</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</webMaster>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aenism.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New logo for Cake DeFi rebrand</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/new-logo-for-cake-defi-rebrand/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/new-logo-for-cake-defi-rebrand/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy working with various startup in the five years since my last post. I joined Cake DeFi in 2019, after being hired by one of its co-founders to lead the design effort. Lots have happened since, which I will talk about in future posts. I&amp;rsquo;d like to share an interesting project that I recently completed – to redesign its logo, as part of a larger brand identity refresh we did in collaboration with Aleph Labs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exciting robotics</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/exciting-robotics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/exciting-robotics/</guid>
      <description>We are seeing increasingly advanced AI and robotics coming out of labs all around the world. I first saw ASIMO in the late 1990s and QRIO in the early 2000s, I was amazed by robotic bipedalism. Twenty years forward, though we are seeing much better locomotion and facial expressions are starting to look a little less creepy and we are definitely in a robotic age, I believe we are still at its dawn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emotional design for telehealth</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/emotional-design-for-telehealth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/emotional-design-for-telehealth/</guid>
      <description>Search for health app ui on pinterest and you will find 9 of 10 examples use a white/cyan color scheme, have minimalistic graphs and beautifully type-set numbers, but not a lot of human.
Sterile sci-fi fantasy is not what healthcare looks like nor should aspire to be.I refuse to accept the sterile sci-fi fantasy aesthetic. It is dehumanizing. I remember walking around in Tokyo and seeing their marketing, ads and graphic design on trains, the street and publications, they are so full of positivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get in Touch</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>I can be reached most effectively by Email and LinkedIn. For bite-size design tidbits, follow me on Twitter. Also feel free to use the contact form below.
powered by Typeform </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Familiarity in healthcare UX</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/familiarity-in-healthcare-ux/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/familiarity-in-healthcare-ux/</guid>
      <description>MyDoc is a health brand with partners including leading global insurers AXA and AIA, and regional pharmaceutical retailer Guardian Pharmacy (Mannings in other regions). Started in 2012 in Singapore, MyDoc aims to integrates all aspects of healthcare into an easy-to-use platform which connects employers, governments and patients to doctors, pharmacies, insurers and laboratories.
Dr Snehal Patel, CEO and Co-Founder of MyDoc was introduced to me by an investor back in 2013 to help drive design in a then fledgling company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uniqlo Next</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/uniqlo-next-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/uniqlo-next-demo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miura-fold map of San Francisco</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/miura-fold-map-of-san-francisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/miura-fold-map-of-san-francisco/</guid>
      <description>The map was inspired by a passage in Walter Benjamin’s _Arcades Project_ where he describes a 19th century map of Paris known as the Plan Taride, which unlike the flimsy paper maps of the day, was a miniature fully-bound book.
Content Highlights 38 spots around the city, including the best tea shop in Chinatown, a mini-park 11 stories in the air, a private library, and a bunch of amazing restaurants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collection of brand and ID work</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/collection-of-brand-and-id-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/collection-of-brand-and-id-work/</guid>
      <description>6degrees Tailored to its essence, a geometrical fit cut for 6degrees &amp;ndash; a self-cleaning and self-updating digital phonebook.
Initially available on Android and now on iOS, 6degrees is a self-updating phonebook that automatically cleans duplicates and backs itself up. One of the first things I did for 6degrees was to refresh their identity.
The old logo although full of homemade goodness was too much like a geek hobby project.6degrees is named after the popular theory originally set out by Frigyes Karinthy and popularized by a play written by John Guare – that everyone and everything is six or fewer steps away, by way of introduction, from any other person in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fear, regression and creativity</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/fear-regression-and-creativity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/fear-regression-and-creativity/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s scary to be a child. We start off as helpless infants totally dependent on our caretakers. As soon as we leave the safety of our mothers&amp;rsquo; wombs, we had to start getting used to fears and anxieties as the world unfolds itself in ever increasing complexity.
I remember a nightmare when i was three, the frightening image of a top hat-wearing skull woke me from sleep. It might have been Baron Samedi but I have never seen him as a child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good taste</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/good-taste/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/good-taste/</guid>
      <description>The widely accepted notion of taste is of a sociological concept defined as a person&amp;rsquo;s personal and cultural patterns of preference. Of what looks good and what is cool. Is there an objective measure of beauty? How does taste work?
Taste or more accurately aesthetic taste is emotional. It&amp;rsquo;s the ability to discern the pleasant and the polar opposite of the emotion of disgust. Like the other senses, we perceive pleasance, beauty and goodness as sensory signals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White room</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/white-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/white-room/</guid>
      <description>Imagine.
You are in an empty white room. Just you in a stark, small empty space. With nothing to do, nothing to entertain yourself with. You fall asleep eventually only to wake up to the same bleakness as before.
Imagine.
Now an empty notebook appears in front of you. Then a pencil.
You now have something to do. You are not bored anymore. Having some writing/drawing materials makes a big difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNIQLO Next</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/uniqlo-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/uniqlo-next/</guid>
      <description>In this article I&amp;rsquo;ll discuss an experimental redesign of a fashion product page from Uniqlo Japan&amp;rsquo;s online shopping website. I imagined how the site would be like a couple of years from now. View the demo
I’ve been wearing American Apparel T-shirts for years and recently switched to Uniqlo when I was finally able to fit into a Japanese size L after losing weight. Uniqlo is much cheaper than AA and I can just buy them in town than pay shipping fees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anticurious hazards</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/anticurious-hazards/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/anticurious-hazards/</guid>
      <description>Nuon is a curious boy. He got it from me. I remember on the day he was born, I was carrying tiny Nuon in my arms as I showed him around the room my wife was staying in. I pointed at various objects and his already keen eyes followed my finger around. There was a glow in his eyes. “Wow” I thought, “he’s going to be an explorer!”
And he is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspiring videos</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/inspiring-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/inspiring-videos/</guid>
      <description>If you do creative work like me you would find the following videos helpful. I&amp;rsquo;ve grouped them to make it easier for you to choose what you want to watch but I recommend you watch all of them.
Personal growth Growing as a designer is like growing up as a person. To become better at something is to take heed from those who have done it. One of the most important advice I had came from this video interview of Ira Glass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teleportation is scary</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/teleportation-is-scary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/teleportation-is-scary/</guid>
      <description>I first came across pjax (pushState + ajax) when I was working on a Rails 4 project which has Turbolinks. Turbolinks isn&amp;rsquo;t pjax per se. It&amp;rsquo;s similar and based on the same philosophy.
How pjax works Instead of re-rendering a full page on every page request, pjax fetches only a fragment of the target page and uses that to replace its counterpart in the current DOM, thereby preserving the surrounding layout, scripts and style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End of passive</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/end-of-passive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/end-of-passive/</guid>
      <description>Human communication progresses in three primary dimensions – relation, distance and fidelity. Relation is about how we are connected. The simplest network is a direct line between two nodes. A face-to-face (one-to-one) dialog for example. A speech is one-to-many. A campfire is many-to-many. With the Morse code, we conquered distance. The telephone allowed us to converse with somebody far away as if he was near. The internet grew similarly. Email started as one-to-one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A child mind</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/a-child-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/a-child-mind/</guid>
      <description>The Riddle Consider this riddle I found spread­ing on Face­book some while ago.
This problem can be solved by children in five to ten minutes, programmers in an hour and people with higher education…
8809 → 6 5555 → 0 7111 → 0 8193 → 3 2172 → 0 8096 → 5 6666 → 4 1111 → 0 3213 → 0 9999 → 4 7662 → 2 7756 → 1 9313 → 1 6855 → 3 0000 → 4 9881 → 5 2222 → 0 5531 → 0 3333 → 0 2581 → ?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
