<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>branding on Aenism</title>
    <link>https://aenism.com/tags/branding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in branding on Aenism</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</webMaster>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aenism.com/tags/branding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New logo for Cake DeFi rebrand</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/new-logo-for-cake-defi-rebrand/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/new-logo-for-cake-defi-rebrand/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy working with various startup in the five years since my last post. I joined Cake DeFi in 2019, after being hired by one of its co-founders to lead the design effort. Lots have happened since, which I will talk about in future posts. I&amp;rsquo;d like to share an interesting project that I recently completed – to redesign its logo, as part of a larger brand identity refresh we did in collaboration with Aleph Labs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collection of brand and ID work</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/collection-of-brand-and-id-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/collection-of-brand-and-id-work/</guid>
      <description>6degrees Tailored to its essence, a geometrical fit cut for 6degrees &amp;ndash; a self-cleaning and self-updating digital phonebook.
Initially available on Android and now on iOS, 6degrees is a self-updating phonebook that automatically cleans duplicates and backs itself up. One of the first things I did for 6degrees was to refresh their identity.
The old logo although full of homemade goodness was too much like a geek hobby project.6degrees is named after the popular theory originally set out by Frigyes Karinthy and popularized by a play written by John Guare – that everyone and everything is six or fewer steps away, by way of introduction, from any other person in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
