<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Healthcare on Aenism</title>
    <link>https://aenism.com/tags/healthcare/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Healthcare on Aenism</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</webMaster>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aenism.com/tags/healthcare/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Emotional Design for Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/emotional-design-for-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/emotional-design-for-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>Search for health app ui on pinterest and you will find 9 of 10 examples use a white/cyan color scheme, have minimalistic graphs and beautifully type-set numbers, but not a lot of human.
Sterile sci-fi fantasy is not what healthcare looks like nor should aspire to be. I refuse to accept the sterile sci-fi fantasy aesthetic. It is dehumanizing. I remember walking around in Tokyo and seeing their marketing, ads and graphic design on trains, the street and publications, they are so full of positivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Familiar Healthcare UX</title>
      <link>https://aenism.com/familiar-healthcare-ux/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hello@aentan.com (AenTan)</author>
      <guid>https://aenism.com/familiar-healthcare-ux/</guid>
      <description>MyDoc is a health brand with partners including leading global insurers AXA and AIA, and regional pharmaceutical retailer Guardian Pharmacy (Mannings in other regions). Started in 2012 in Singapore, MyDoc aims to integrates all aspects of healthcare into an easy-to-use platform which connects employers, governments and patients to doctors, pharmacies, insurers and laboratories.
Dr Snehal Patel, CEO and Co-Founder of MyDoc was introduced to me by an investor back in 2013 to help drive design in a then fledgling company.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>